bqool.com 2016-06-07

# Privacy Policy - BQool

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage, and at every point where private information may be requested. This Privacy Policy applies to BQool websites, services, and products that collect data and display these terms.

#### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

You can access all your private information collected online via the tool, admin, and account setting pages of your account. You can correct factual errors in your private information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your private information.

#### The Information We Collect

We collect and store information from you when you register on our Site or setup a new online marketplace account. When registering or ordering on our Site, you will be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, credit card information, and online marketplace account credentials, as well as certain related information such as your company name and website name. Alternatively, you may anonymously visit our Site.

#### The Way We Use Information

BQool may use the personal information you provide: to operate or improve the products, services, and other features offered to you when you visit or shop at the Site (the “Service”) and tailor the Service to your needs; for billing, identification, and authentication; to contact and communicate with you about the Service and your use of the Service; to send you marketing materials (subject to your opt-out option); for research purposes; and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service. BQool may also share your personal information with its third party service providers (such as credit card processors and hosting partners) to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other services we use to operate the Service and maintain a high quality user experience. We do not permit our service providers to use the personal information you provide for their marketing purposes. In particular, we do not permit our credit card processors to store, retain, or use your billing information for any purpose except for credit card processing on BQool’s behalf. BQool may also disclose personal information as necessary to: (i) comply with the law or pursuant to subpoena; (ii) enforce or apply our Terms of Use, Terms of Service, or other agreements or policies; or (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of BQool, our users, or others. By using the Service, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information as described in this notice.  
Other than as provided for in this notice, your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or provided to any other company for any reason without your consent. We never use or share your private information in ways unrelated to those described in this notice without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise limit such unrelated uses. 

#### How We Use Cookies

Cookies allow a web server to identify your computer and web browser, and tailor web pages and/or login information to your preferences. Cookies are small software files stored temporarily or placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us promptly display the information you need to use the capabilities of the Services and other information which we consider to be of interest of you. BQool uses cookies in order to enable the sites or service provider systems to recognize your browser and remember certain information. By gathering and remembering information about your website preferences through cookies, we can provide a better web and shopping experience. Cookies, however, do not give us access to your computer, and the information we collect through cookies does not include personal information.

#### California Online Privacy Protect Act Compliance

BQool is in compliance with California Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Public Forums

The Service (including the BQool Website) offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

#### Children’s Personal Information

To ensure compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), BQool does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13.

#### Third Party Websites, Services, and Applications

Please be aware that other websites and services, including the websites of third parties that you connect with through our Service or Site, may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third party websites, services, or applications.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any revised Privacy Policies on our homepage and at every point where private information may be requested.

#### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at support@bqool.com
